<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="arr">
        <item>\t\tPeople "don't" make mistakes because of ignorance, but because they think they are intelligent.</item>
        <item> \t\t"If you want to know what a person's like, take a good look at how they treat their enemies, not friends."</item>
        <item>  \t\t"Sometimes people don't notice the things we do for them until we stop doing them."</item>
        <item>\t\tListen carefully to how a person speaks about other people to you.This is how they will speak about you to other people.</item>
        <item>\t\tMost people "don't" listen with the intent to understand; they listen with the intent to reply.</item>
        <item>\t\tA person who likes the same
             things you like maybe like you.</item>
        <item>\t\tSometimes you will never know the value of  something,
           	 until it becomes a memory</item>
        <item>\t\tForgiveness does not change the past,but it does enlarge the future.</item>
        <item>\t\tDoing what you like is FREEDOM.Liking what you do is HAPPINESS.</item>
        <item>\t\tYou are going to come across people in your life who will say all the right words.</item>
        <item>\t\tTake wrong way is not terrifying, just not knowing where to go is terrifying.</item>
        <item>\t\tWhen you mature,you will understand that what you really need is not a good love</item>
        <item>\t\tPeople do not leave because things are hard.They leave because it is no longer worth it.</item>
        <item>\t\tWhen you are up, your friends know who you are.
			  When you are down, you know who your friends are.</item>
        <item>\t\tThere is no way to wake someone who is pretending to sleep.Just as there is</item>
        <item>\t\tIf you do not even cry anymore, you will never get real smile.</item>
        <item>\t\tMaking others hurt as easily as throwing a stone into the sea,but you don not know </item>
        <item>\t\tIf they want to do something, they will find the ways to do, if they do not want to do, they will find the reasons to refuse.</item>
        <item>\t\tLove makes people forget the time and the time makes people forget </item>
        <item>\t\tThe peaceful silence between two people who know each other is very different from the confused silence </item>
        <item>\t\tMy heart is narrow, only one place to store you.</item>
        <item>\t\tThere is a truth that never changes:The sun of yesterday can not dry clothes today.</item>
        <item>\t\tAn unclearly relationship just like an empty petrol vehicle. You can sit on it</item>
        <item>\t\tLife is like a train on rails. Can only go forward, right or left</item>
        <item>\t\tTrying to be better others not just by trying to be better than yourself yesterday.</item>
        <item>\t\tSomeday, when you hurt by whom you really love, you will understand how much pain I have been by you.</item>
        <item>\t\tDo not just look at the results that hasty evaluate efforts of others.</item>
        <item>\t\tIn fact,in this world no one is stupid or smart, but people are honest or sly.</item>
        <item>\t\tLife as a stage, you can play a role in this, but can also play a supporting role in another.</item>
        <item>\t\tIt would be cruel for you when you love someone but just got their pity back. You know? </item>
        <item>\t\tWhen Someone Says You have Changed, It Simply Means You have to Stopped Living Your Life Their Way.</item>
        <item>\t\tSometimes we don not need advice.We just need somebody to listen.</item>
        <item>\t\tMove on.It is just a chapter in the past, but don not close the book, just turn the page.</item>
        <item>\t\tToo soft-hearted with the person who hurt you are cruel to yourself.</item>
        <item>\t\tEffort is not necessarily bring success,if you fail, you still get experience. But if you do not try, you will not have anything. </item>
        <item>\t\tIt is very easy to refuse someone when they need you. But you listen to the denial when you need them.</item>
        <item>\tHow much nostalgia to be called love? \n
			  \tHow much waiting to exchange a sincere love?\n 
			  \tHow much forgotten to become stranger?</item>
        <item>In love, no matter who comes first,who comes later, who is right, who is wrong. Just was not love, it is the 3rd person!</item>
        <item>You can not controlnevery situation occursn\nBut you can completely control  your thoughts and your attitude.</item>
        <item>\t\tIt is easier to fool people than to convince them that they have been fooled.</item>
        <item>\t\tWhen people love each other, this world will become little cramped. When it ends, just a street corner becomes extremely large around.</item>
        <item>\t\tWe live life looking forward and only understand it fully looking backward.</item>
        <item>\t\tNever say all you known. And never believe all you hear.</item>
        <item>\t\tIf you can not be a pencil to write anyone is happiness,then try to be a nice eraser to remove someone is sadness.</item>
        <item>\t\tLife is like riding a bicycle To keep your balance you must keep moving.</item>
        <item>\t\tForgive to someone who hurt you. It is a gift you give for them. Forget to someone who hurt you. It is a gift you give for yourself.</item>
        <item>\t\tIt is better to be hated for what you are than to be loved for what you are not.</item>
        <item>\t\tTher people hurt you first is their fault, but if then you get them hurt again, that is your fault.</item>
        <item>\t\tNever joke with other people is feelings You can win and you will lose them forever.</item>
        <item>\t\tGetting angry\nis punishing yourself with other people is mistakes.</item>
        <item>\t\tSome people choose to stay single simply because they are tired of giving everything and ending up with nothing.</item>
        <item>\t\tMistakes\nmade in life are our lessons in disguise. And sometimes the best lessons learned, came from the worst mistakes made.</item>
        <item>\t\tThe worst feeling is when you decide to forgive someone,but just that moment you discovered that they were trying to deceive you at the last minute.</item>
        <item>\t\tDon not ever mistake my silence for ignorance, my calmness for acceptance, and my countermarch for weakness.</item>
        <item>\t\tSometimes\nwhat you want is not what you get, but what you get in the end is so much better than what you wanted.</item>
        <item>\t\tNever forget 3 types of people in your life:\n
				1.Who helped you in your difficult times.\n
				2. Who left you in your difficult times.\n
				3. Who put you in difficult times.</item>
        <item>It is better to know and be disappointed, than to never know and always wonder.!</item>
        <item>\t\tAn intelligent person is like a river,the deeper the less noise.</item>
        <item>\t\tThere are meetings are believed that we will be together forever,but then we are also apart from each other.</item>
        <item>\t\tIt takes years to build up trust, but only seconds to destroy it.</item>
        <item>\t\tPeople comes together when they do not understand each other. And people leaves together when they clearly knew each other.</item>
        <item>\t\tA funny story cannot make us laugh many times, so why do we always have to be sad for an unhappy?</item>
        <item>\t\tWomen hold the men back with tears, but also useless. Men want to hurt women just saying: "I don't love you."</item>
        <item>\t\tForgive others, not because they deserve forgiveness, but because you deserve peace.</item>
        <item>\t\t"Waiting for someone is not scary, frightening thing is that you don't know how long should you wait for him.."</item>
        <item>\t\tNever lie to someone who trusts you and never trust someone that lies to you.</item>
        <item>\t\t"Although the memory makes people hurt when they think about it, they can't forget it, not because it is beautiful.."</item>
        <item>\t\tIf you want to make your dreams come true, the first thing you have to do is wake up.</item>
        <item>\t\tYou never know how strong you are until being strong is the only choice you have.</item>
        <item>\t\t"The way people treat you is a statement about who they are as a human being. It's not a statement about you.!"</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Anh Van -->
    <string-array name="data">
        <item>People do not make mistakes because of ignorance, but because they think they are intelligent.
				\n\nNgười ta thường không mắc sai lầm vì ngu dốt, mà vì tưởng là mình thông minh.</item>
   
        <item>"If you want to know what a person's like, take a good look at how they treat their enemies, not friends."
\n\nNếu bạn muốn biết bản chất của một người như thế nào, hãy nhìn cách người đó đối xử với kẻ thù của họ, chứ không phải với bạn bè.</item>
        <item>"Sometimes people don't notice the things we do for them until we stop doing them."
\n\nĐôi khi, người ta không chú ý đến những gì chúng ta làm cho họ cho đến khi chúng ta không làm nữa.</item>
        <item>Listen carefully to how a person speaks about other people to you.This is how they will speak about you to other people.
\n\nHãy lắng nghe thật cẩn thận khi một người nói với bạn về một ai đó. Vì đó sẽ là cách mà họ nói với một ai đó về bạn.</item>
        <item>Most people do not listen with the intent to understand; they listen with the intent to reply.
\n\nNhiều người nghe không phải để hiểu. Họ nghe chỉ để đáp trả.</item>
        <item>A person who likes the same things you like maybe like you.
			But if a person tries to like things you like because of you, then surely that she/he really loves you.\n\n 
			Một người cùng thích những điều bạn thích có lẽ thích bạn. 
			Nhưng nếu một người vì bạn mà cố gắng thích điều bạn thích, thì chắc chắn là người đó thật sự rất yêu bạn.</item>
        <item>Sometimes you will never know the value of something,until it becomes a memory.\n\n
			Đôi khi bạn sẽ không biết được giá trị của một khoảnh khắc cho đến khi nó trở thành kí ức.</item>
        <item>Forgiveness does not change the past, but it does enlarge the future.\n\n
			Sự tha thứ không thể thay đổi quá khứ, nhưng nó cho tương lai một cơ hội.</item>
        <item>Doing what you like is FREEDOM. Liking what you do is HAPPINESS.\n\n
			Làm những gì bạn thích, đó là Tự Do. Thích những gì bạn làm, đó là Hạnh Phúc.</item>
        <item>You are going to come across people in your life who will say all the right
             words at all the right times. But in the end, it is always their actions you 
             should judge them by. It is actions, not words, that matter.
			\n\nBạn sẽ đi qua những người trong cuộc sống của bạn, những người mà họ sẽ nói toàn 
			là những lời hay ý đẹp đúng vào những thời điểm tốt. Nhưng cuối cùng, hành động của họ 
			mới là cái mà bạn phải đánh giá.Đánh giá một con người là ở hành động, không phải lời nói.</item>
        <item>Take wrong way is not terrifying, just not knowing where to go is terrifying.\n\n
			Đi sai đường không đáng sợ, đáng sợ là không biết mình phải đi đâu.</item>
        <item>When you mature, you will understand that what you really need is not a good love,
             that is the one who has the patience to tolerate you for a lifetime.\n\n
			Đến khi bạn trưởng thành, bạn sẽ hiểu rằng cái bạn thật sự cần không phải là một tình yêu đẹp,
 			mà là 1 người có đủ kiên nhẫn để bao dung bạn suốt đời.</item>
        <item>People do not leave because things are hard. They leave because it is no longer worth it.\n\n
			Người ta không rời bỏ vì khó khăn, họ rời bỏ vì điều đó không còn xứng đáng nữa.</item>
        <item>When you are up, your friends know who you are
			When you are down, you know who your friends are.
			\n\nKhi đứng lên, bạn bè sẽ biết bạn là ai. Khi ngã xuống, bạn sẽ biết ai mới là bạn bè của bạn.</item>
        <item>There is no way to wake someone who is pretending to sleep.Just as there is no way to touch someone who does not love you.
			\n\nBạn không có cách nào đánh thức một người chỉ giả vờ ngủ. Cũng như không có cách nào làm cảm động một người không hề yêu bạn.</item>
        <item>If you do not even cry anymore, you will never get real smile.
			\n\nNếu bạn không còn khóc được nữa, thì bạn cũng không bao giờ có được nụ cười thật sự. </item>
        <item>Making others hurt as easily as throwing a stone into the sea, but you do not know that how deep the stone may be down.\n\n
			Làm cho người khác tổn thương có thể dễ dàng như ném một hòn đá xuống biển, nhưng bạn không biết được rằng hòn đá đó có thể xuống tới sâu cỡ nào.</item>
        <item>If they want to do something, they will find the ways to do, if they do not want to do, they will find the reasons to refuse.
			\n\nNếu muốn làm, người ta sẽ tìm cách. Nếu không muốn, người ta sẽ tìm lý do.</item>
        <item>Love makes people forget the time and the time makes people forget that love existed.
			\n\nTình yêu khiến người ta quên đi thời gian, còn thời gian khiến người ta quên đi tình yêu đã từng tồn tại.</item>
        <item>The peaceful silence between two people who know each other is very different from the confused silence between two people who have nothing to say to each other.
			\n\nSự im lặng ổn thoả giữa hai người quá hiểu nhau rất khác với sự im lặng bối rối giữa hai người không có gì để nói với nhau…</item>
        <item>My heart is narrow, only one place to store you. Your heart is wide but too cramped because of store too many people, no place for me.
			\n\nTrái tim tôi nhỏ hẹp, chỉ chứa đủ một mình bạn. Trái tim bạn rộng lớn, nhưng lại chật chội vì chứa quá nhiều người, không có chỗ cho tôi.</item>
        <item>There is a truth that never changes: The sun of yesterday can not dry clothes today. Do not regret the past. Also do not worry for the future. Take a good living for the present.
			\n\nCó một chân lý không bao giờ thay đổi: Cái nắng của ngày hôm qua không thể phơi khô quần áo của ngày hôm nay. Đừng nuối tiếc quá khứ. Cũng đừng quá lo lắng cho tương lai. Hãy sống tốt cho hiện tại. </item>
        <item>An unclearly relationship just like an empty petrol vehicle. You can sit on it as long as you like, but it will not take you anywhere.
\n\nMột mối quan hệ không rõ ràng cũng giống như một chiếc xe cạn xăng. Bạn có thể ngồi trên đó bao lâu bạn thích, nhưng nó sẽ không đưa bạn đi đến đâu cả.</item>
        <item>Life is like a train on rails. Can only go forward, right or left, cannot turn around!
\n\nCuộc sống giống như đoàn tàu chạy trên đường ray. Chỉ có thể tiến về phía trước, rẽ phải hay rẽ trái, không thế quay đầu trở lại.</item>
        <item>Trying to be better others not just by trying to be better than yourself yesterday.
\n\nCố gắng để hơn người khác chi bằng cố gắng để hơn chính mình ngày hôm qua.</item>
        <item>Someday, when you hurt by whom you really love, you will understand how much pain I have been by you.!
\n\nMột ngày nào đó, khi anh đau vì người anh yêu thực sự, anh sẽ hiểu em đã từng đau vì anh như thế nào.</item>
        <item>Do not just look at the results that hasty evaluate efforts of others.
\n\nĐừng chỉ nhìn vào kết quả mà vội vàng đánh giá sự cố gắng của người khác.</item>
        <item>In fact, in this world no one is stupid or smart, but people are honest or sly.
\n\nThật ra trên đời này đâu có người ngu ngốc hay kẻ thông minh, mà chỉ có người thật thà và kẻ ranh mãnh.</item>
        <item>Life as a stage, you can play a role in this, but can also play a supporting role in another. So, let is define its role and fulfill it,
because, no matter what, there will always be dedicated to play yourself.
\n\nĐời người như một sân khấu, bạn có thể là vai chính trong vở kịch này, nhưng cũng có thể là vai phụ trong vở kịch khác. Vậy, hãy xác định vai diễn 
của mình và hoàn thành tốt nó, bởi vì, dù thế nào đi nữa, sẽ luôn có vở kịch dành riêng cho chính bạn.</item>
        <item>It would be cruel for you when you love someone but just got their pity back. You know? Sometimes coldness and indifference of someone make you more comfortable.
\n\nSẽ thật tàn nhẫn khi bạn yêu thương ai đó nhưng chỉ nhận lại sự thương hại từ họ. Bạn biết không? đôi khi sự lạnh lùng và hờ hững của ai đó lại khiến bạn dễ chịu hơn. </item>
        <item>When Someone Says You have Changed, It Simply Means You have to Stopped Living Your Life Their Way.
\n\nKhi ai đó nói rằng bạn đã thay đổi, điều đó đơn giản có nghĩa là bạn không còn sống cuộc sống của mình theo cách của họ (theo cách mà họ muốn</item>
        <item>Sometimes we don not need advice.We just need somebody to listen....
\n\nĐôi khi chúng ta không cần lời khuyên. Chúng ta chỉ cần ai đó để lắng nghe... </item>
        <item>Move on. It is just a chapter in the past, but don not close the book, just turn the page.
\n\nHãy tiếp tục bước đi. Đó chỉ là một phần nhỏ trong quá khứ. Đừng đóng cả quyển sách lại, hãy chỉ lật sang trang. </item>
        <item>Too soft-hearted with the person who hurt you are cruel to yourself.
\n\nQúa mềm lòng với người đã làm tổn thương bạn chính là tàn nhẫn với bản thân mình.</item>
        <item>Effort is not necessarily bring success, if you fail, you still get experience. But if you do not try, you will not have anything. 
\n\nSự cố gắng không nhất định sẽ mang lại thành công, nếu bạn thất bại, bạn vẫn có được kinh nghiệm. Nhưng nếu bạn không cố gắng, bạn sẽ không được gì cả.</item>
        <item>It is very easy to refuse someone when they need you. But you listen to the denial when you need them, you will know it is really painful feeling!
\n\nThật dễ dàng khi bạn từ chối ai đó khi họ cần bạn. Nhưng đến khi bạn nghe lời từ chối lúc bạn cần họ, bạn sẽ hiểu cảm giác đó thật sự rất đau. </item>
        <item>How much nostalgia to be called love? 
How much waiting to exchange a sincere love? 
How much forgotten to become stranger?
\n\n\Bao nhiêu nỗi nhớ để được gọi là yêu?
Bao nhiêu chờ đợi để đổi một tình yêu chân thành?
Bao nhiêu quên lãng để trở thành xa lạ?</item>
        <item>In love, no matter who comes first, who comes later, who is right, who is wrong. Just was not love, it is the 3rd person!
\n\nTrong tình yêu, bất luận là ai đến trước, ai đến sau, ai đúng, ai sai. Chỉ cần là người không được yêu thương, thì đó là kẻ thứ 3.!</item>
        <item>You can not control every situation occurs. But you can completely control your thoughts and your attitude.
\n\nBạn không thể kiểm soát được mọi tình huống xảy ra. Nhưng bạn hoàn toàn có thể kiểm soát được suy nghĩ và thái độ của mình. </item>
        <item>It is easier to fool people than to convince them that they have been fooled.
\n\nLừa gạt ai đó dễ dàng hơn việc thuyết phục ai đó rằng họ đã bị lừa.</item>
        <item>When people love each other, this world will become little cramped. When it ends, just a street corner becomes extremely large around. 
\n\nKhi người ta yêu nhau, cả thế giới này cũng sẽ trở nên nhỏ bé chật hẹp. Khi người ta đã hết yêu, một góc phố thôi cũng trở nên rộng lớn loanh quanh vô cùng. </item>
        <item>We live life looking forward and only understand it fully looking backward.
\n\nChúng ta phải sống cuộc đời mình bằng cách nhìn về phía trước, và chỉ có thể hoàn toàn hiểu được nó khi nhìn lại phía sau. </item>
        <item>Never say all you know. And never believe all you hear.
\n\nĐừng bao giờ nói tất cả những gì bạn biết. Và đừng bao giờ tin tất cả những gì bạn nghe.</item>
        <item>If you can not be a pencil to write anyone is happiness, then try to be a nice eraser to remove someone is sadness.
\n\nNếu bạn không thể trở thành cây bút chì để viết nên niềm hạnh phúc cho một ai, thì hãy cố gắng trở thành một cục tẩy tốt để xoá đi nỗi bất hạnh của ai đó.</item>
        <item>Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance you must keep moving.
\n\nCuộc sống giống như việc lái một chiếc xe đạp. Để giữ được thăng bằng, bạn phải tiếp tục di chuyển. </item>
        <item>Forgive to someone who hurt you. It is a gift you give for them. Forget to someone who hurt you. It is a gift you give for yourself.
\n\nTha thứ cho người đã làm tổn thương bạn. Là một món quà bạn dành cho họ. Quên đi người đã làm tổn thương bạn. Là một món quà bạn dành cho chính bạn.</item>
        <item>It is better to be hated for what you are than to be loved for what you are not.
\n\nGhét những gì bạn có tốt hơn là yêu những gì bạn không có.</item>
        <item>Ther people hurt you first is their fault, but if then you get them hurt again, that is your fault.
\n\nNgười khác tổn thương bạn lần thứ nhất là lỗi của họ, nhưng nếu sau đó bạn bị họ tổn thương lần nữa, thì đó là do lỗi của bạn.</item>
        <item>Never joke with other people is feelings. You can win, and you will lose them forever.
\n\nĐừng bao giờ đùa cợt với cảm xúc của người khác. Bạn có thể thắng, và cũng có thể bạn sẽ mất họ mãi mãi. </item>
        <item>Getting angry is punishing yourself with other people is mistakes.
\n\nNổi giận là đem lỗi lầm của người khác trừng phạt bản thân mình. </item>
        <item>Some people choose to stay single simply because they are tired of giving everything and ending up with nothing.
\n\nMột số người chọn sống độc thân đơn giản vì họ quá mệt mỏi với việc cho đi tất cả mọi thứ và rốt cuộc chẳng được gì.</item>
        <item>Mistakes made in life are our lessons in disguise. And sometimes, the best lessons learned, came from the worst mistakes made.
\nNhững bài học của chúng ta được nguỵ trang bởi những sai lầm trong cuộc sống. Và đôi khi, bài học hay nhất mà chúng ta được học, đến từ những sai lầm tồi tệ nhất. </item>
        <item>The worst feeling is when you decide to forgive someone, but just that moment you discovered that they were trying to deceive you at the last minute.
\n\nCảm giác tồi tệ nhất là khi bạn quyết định tha thứ cho một ai đó, nhưng đúng vào lúc đó bạn phát hiện ra rằng họ vẫn cố gắng lừa dối bạn đến phút cuối cùng.</item>
        <item>Don not ever mistake my silence for ignorance, my calmness for acceptance, and my countermarch for weakness.
\n\nĐừng bao giờ nhầm lẫn giữa sự im lặng của tôi với sự thiếu hiểu biết, giữa sự điềm tĩnh của tôi với sự chấp nhận, và sự từ bỏ của tôi với sự yếu đuối.</item>
        <item>Sometimes what you want is not what you get, but what you get in the end is so much better than what you wanted. 
\n\nĐôi khi những gì bạn muốn không phải là những gì bạn nhận được, nhưng những gì bạn nhận được cuối cùng tốt hơn rất nhiều so với những gì bạn muốn.</item>
        <item>Never forget 3 types of people:\n
1.Who helped you in your difficult times.\n
2. Who left you in your difficult times.\n
3. Who put you in difficult times.\n
\n\n
Đừng bao giờ quên ba loại người trong cuộc đời của bạn :
1. Người giúp đỡ bạn khi bạn gặp khó khăn
2. Người rời bỏ bạn khi bạn gặp khó khăn
3. Người đặt bạn vào khó khăn. </item>
        <item>It is better to know and be disappointed, than to never know and always wonder.!
\n\nThà biết rồi thất vọng còn hơn không bao giờ biết và luôn băn khoăn</item>
        <item>An intelligent person is like a river, the deeper the less noise.
\n\nMột người thông minh sẽ như một dòng sông, càng sâu càng ít ồn ào. </item>
        <item>There are meetings are believed that we will be together forever, but then we are also apart from each other. There are separations are believed that we will meet again, but no one knew that once turned away is forever lost to each other.
\n\nCó những cuộc gặp gỡ tưởng rằng sẽ bên nhau mãi, nhưng rồi cũng phải chia ly. Có những cuộc chia ly tưởng rằng sẽ còn gặp lại, nhưng có ai hiểu rằng, một lần quay lưng là mất nhau mãi mãi.</item>
        <item>It takes years to build up trust, but only seconds to destroy it.
\n\nNiềm tin phải cần rất nhiều năm để tạo dựng, nhưng chỉ mất vài giây để đạp đổ nó. </item>
        <item>People comes together when they do not understand each other. And people leaves together when they clearly knew each other.
\n\nNgười ta đến với nhau khi chưa hiểu gì về nhau. Và, người ta rời xa nhau khi đã quá hiểu nhau. </item>
        <item>A funny story cannot make us laugh many times, so why do we always have to be sad for an unhappy?
\n\nMột câu chuyện vui không thể làm chúng ta cười nhiều lần, vậy tại sao chúng ta lại buồn mãi vì một chuyện không vui? </item>
        <item>Women hold the men back with tears, but also useless. Men want to hurt women just saying: "I don't love you."
\n\nPhụ nữ níu kéo đàn ông bằng nước mắt, nhưng cũng vô dụng thôi. Đàn ông muốn phụ nữ tổn thương chỉ cần 1 câu: "Anh không yêu em".</item>
        <item>Forgive others, not because they deserve forgiveness, but because you deserve peace.
\n\nHãy tha thứ cho người khác, không phải bởi vì họ xứng đáng được tha thứ, mà vì bạn xứng đáng được bình yên. </item>
        <item>"Waiting for someone is not scary, frightening thing is that you don't know how long should you wait for him. How long to wait is not scary, the most frightening thing is waiting to finally you realize who you waited entirely unworthy."
\n\nChờ đợi một người thì không đáng sợ, điều đáng sợ là bạn không biết mình phải chờ đợi bao lâu. Chờ đợi bao lâu cũng không đáng sợ, điều đáng sợ nhất là chờ đợi cho đến cuối cùng bạn mới nhận ra người mà bạn chờ đợi hoàn toàn không xứng đáng. </item>
        <item>Never lie to someone who trusts you and never trust someone that lies to you.
\n\nĐừng bao giờ lừa dối người đã tin tưởng bạn, và đừng bao giờ tin tưởng người đã từng lừa dối bạn. </item>
        <item>"Although the memory makes people hurt when they think about it, they can't forget it, not because it is beautiful, but because it has gone and never come back again."
\n\nNgười ta thường không thể quên đi kỷ niệm, cho dù nó khiến họ phải đau đớn khi nghĩ đến, không phải vì nó đẹp, mà là vì nó đã qua đi và không bao giờ trở lại nữa.</item>
        <item>If you want to make your dreams come true, the first thing you have to do is wake up.
\n\nNếu bạn muốn biến giấc mơ của mình trở thành sự thật, việc đầu tiên bạn cần phải làm là thức dậy.!</item>
        <item>You never know how strong you are until being strong is the only choice you have.
\n\nBạn sẽ không biết mình mạnh mẽ như thế nào cho đến khi mạnh mẽ là sự chọn lựa duy nhất.! </item>
        <item>"The way people treat you is a statement about who they are as a human being. It's not a statement about you. So don't mind about the person always defame you, it shows that they don't have anything nice to say about themselves!"
\n\nCách người khác đối xử với bạn thể hiện con người của họ như thế nào, chứ không phải bạn.! Vì vậy đừng quá bận tâm về những người hay nói xấu bạn, điều đó cho thấy họ không có bất cứ điều gì tốt để nói về bản thân mình.! </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>