<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="noidunganh">
        <item>
\t\t INTRODUCTION\n
\tThe power of Affirmations 
\n\n\tToday is a new day. Today is a day for you to begin creating a joyous, fulfilling life. 
Today is the day to begin release all your limitations. Today is the day for you to learn the secrets 
of life. You can change your life for the better. You already have the tools within you to do so. 
These tools are your thoughts and your beliefs. Inthis book, I will teach you how to use these 
tools to improve the quality of your life.
\n\n\tFor those of you who aren’t familiar with the benefits of positive affirmations, I’d like to 
explain a little about them. An affirmation is really anything you say or think. However a lot of 
what we normally say and think is quite negative and doesn’t create good experiences for us. We 
have to retrain our thinking and speaking into positive patterns ifwe want to change our lives. 
\n\n\tAn affirmation opens the door. It’s a beginning point on the path to change. In essence, 
you’re saying to yoursubconscious mind: “I am taking responsibility. I am aware that there is 
something I can do to change.”When I talk about doing affirmations, I mean consciously 
choosing words that will either help eliminate something from your life or helpcreate something 
new in your life.
\n\n\tEvery thought you think and every word you speak is an affirmation. All of our self-talk, 
our internal dialogue, is a stream of affirmations. You’re using affirmations every moment 
whether you know it or not. You’re affirming and creating your life experiences with every word 
and thought.
\n\n\tYour beliefs are merely habitual thinking patterns that you learned as a child. Many of 
them work very well for you. Other beliefs may be limiting your ability to create the very things 
you say you want. What you want and what you believe you deserve may be very different. You 
need to pay attention to your thoughts so that you can begin to eliminate the ones creating 
experiences you do not want in your life.
\n\n\tPlease realize that every complaint is an affirmation of something you think you don’t 
want in your life. Every time you get angry, you’reaffirming that you wantmore anger in your 
life. Every time you feel like a victim, you’re affirming that you want to continue to feel like a 
victim. If you fell that life isn’t giving you what you wantin your world, then it’s certain that you 
will never have the goodies that Life gives to others – that is, until you change the way you think 
and talk.
\n\n\tYou’re not a bad person for thinking the way you do. You’ve just never learned how to think and talk. 
People throughoutthe world are just now beginning to learn that our thoughts 
create our experiences. Your parents probably didn’t know this, so they couldn’t possibly teach it 
to you. They taught youhow to look at life in the way that their parents taught them. So nobody is 
wrong. However, it’s time for all of us to wake upand begin to consciously create our lives in a 
way that pleases and supports us. You can do it. I can do it. We all can do it – we just need to 
learn how. So let’s get to it.

\n\n\tThroughout this book, I’ll talk about affirmations in general, and then I’ll get to specific 
areas of life and show you how to make positive changes in your health, your finances, your love 
life, and so on. This is a small book, because once you learn how to use affirmations, then you 
can apply the principles in all situations.
\n\n\tSome people say that “affirmations don’t work”(which is an affirmation in itself), when 
what they mean is that they don’t know how to use them correctly. They may say: “My prosperity 
is growing,” but then think, “Oh, this is stupid, I know it won’t work”. Which affirmation do you 
think will win out? The negative one, of course, because it’s part of a long-standing,habitual way 
of looking at life. Sometimes people will say their affirmations once a day and complain the rest 
of the time. It will take a long time for affirmations to work if they’re done that way. The 
complaining affirmations will always win, because there are moreof them and they’re usually 
said with great feeling. 
\n\n\tHowever, saying affirmations is only part of the process. Whatyou do the rest of the day 
and night is even more important. The secret to having your affirmations work quickly and 
consistently is to prepare an atmosphere for them to grow in. Affirmations are like seeds planted 
in soil. Poor soil, poor growth. Rich soil, abundant growth. The more you choose to think 
thoughts that make you fell good, the quick the affirmations work. 
\n\n\tSo think happy thoughts, it’s that simple. And it is doable. The way you choose to think, 
right now, is just that – a choice. You may not realize it because you’ve thought this way for so 
long, but it really is a choice. Now … today … this moment … you can choose to change your 
thinking. Your life won’t turn around overnight, but if you’re consistent and make the choice on 
daily basis to think thoughts that make you fell good,you’ll definitely make positive changes in 
every area of your life.
\n\n\tI wake up each morning with blessings and gratitude for the wonderful life I lead, and I 
make the choice to think happy thoughts no matter what others are doing. No, I don’t do this 100 
percent of the time, but I am up to about 75 or 80 percent right now, and it’s made a big 
difference in how much I enjoy life and how much good just seems to flow into my everyday 
world.
\n\n\tThe only moment you ever live inis this moment. It’s the only time you have any control 
over. “Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, today is a gift, which is why we call it the 
present”. If you don’t choose to feel good inthis moment, then how can you create future 
moments that are abundant and fun?
\n\n\tHow do you fell right now? Do you feel good? Do you fell bad? What are you current emotions? 
What is your gut feeling? Would you like to feel better? Then reach for a better feeling or 
thought. If you fell bad in any way – sad, grumpy, bitter, resentful, angry, fearful, guilty, 
depressed, jealous, critical, and so on – then you’ve temporarily lost your connection to the flow 
of good experiences thatthe Universe has waiting for you. Don’t waste your thoughts on blame. 
No person, place, or thing has any control over your feelings because they don’t think in your 
mind.

\n\n\tThis is also why you really have no control over others – you see, you can’t control their 
thoughts. No one can control another unless that person gives permission. So you want to be 
aware of this powerful mind you have. You can take total control over your own thinking. It’s the 
only thing you’ll ever have total control of. What you choose to think is whatyou’ll get in life. 
I’ve chosen to think thoughts of joy and appreciation, and you can, too.
\n\n\tWhat kinds of thoughts makeyou feel good? Thoughts of love, appreciation, gratitude, 
joyful childhood experiences? Thoughts in which you rejoice thatyou’re alive and bless your 
body with love? Do you truly enjoy this present moment and get excited about tomorrow? 
Thinking these kinds of thoughts is an act of loving yourself creates miracles in your life.
\n\n\tNow let’s get to the affirmations. Doing affirmations is consciously choosing to think 
certain thoughts that will create positive results in the future. They create a focal point that will 
allow you to be changing your thinking. Affirmative statements are going beyond the reality of 
the present into the creation of the future through the words you use in the now.
\n\n\tWhen you choose to say “I am very prosperous”, you may actually have very little money 
in the bank at the moment, but what you’re doing is planting seeds for future prosperity. Each 
time you repeat this statement, you’re reaffirming the seeds you’re planted in the atmosphere of 
your mind. That’s why you wantit to be a happy atmosphere. Things grow more quickly in 
fertile, rich soil.
\n\n\tIt’s important for you to always say your affirmations in the present tense. For example, 
typical affirmations would start: “I have …” or “I am …” If you say,“I am going to …” or “I will 
have …” then your thought stays out there in the future. The Universe takes your thoughts and 
words very literally and gives you what you say you want. Always. This is another reason to 
maintain a happy mental atmosphere. It’s easier to think in positive affirmations when you fell 
good.
\n\n\tThink of it this way: Every thought you think counts, so don’t waste your precious 
thoughts. Every negative thought pushes good away; it keeps it just out of your reach. How many 
times in your life have you almost gotten something good and it seemed to be snatched away at 
the last moment? If you could remember what yourmental atmosphere was like at those times, 
you’d have the answer. Too many negative thoughts create a barrier against positive affirmations. 
If you say “I don’t want to be sick anymore”, this is not an affirmation for good health. 
You have to state clearly what you dowant. “I accept perfect health now”. \n\n
“I hate this car” does not bring you a wonderful new car because you’re not being clear. 
Even if you do get a new car, ina short time you’ll probably hate it, because that’s what you’ve 
been affirming. If you want a new car, then say something like this: “I have a beautiful new car 
that suits all of my needs”. \n\n
\tYou’ll hear some people saying, “Life sucks!” (which is a terrible affirmation). Can you 
imagine what experiences that statement will attract to you? Of course, it isn’t Life that sucks, it’s 
your thinking that sucks. That thought will help you feel terrible.And when you feel terrible, no 
good can come into your life. \n\n
Don’t waste time arguing for your limitations: poor relationships, problems, illnesses, 
poverty, and so on. The more you talk about the problem, the more you anchor it in place. Don’t 
blame others for what’s seemingly wrong in your life – that’s just another waste of time. 
\n\n\tRemember, you’re under the laws of your own consciousness, your own thoughts, and you attract 
specific experiences to you as a result of the way you think.  \n\n
When you change your thinking process, then everything in your life will also change. 
You’ll be amazed and delighted to see how people, places, things, and circumstances can change. 
Blame is just another negative affirmation, and you don’t want to waste your precious thoughts 
on it. Instead, learn to turn your negative affirmations into positive ones. 
For instance: \n\n
 I have to body.  BECOMES  I love and appreciate my body. \n\n
 I never have enough money.  BECOMES Money flows into my life in an 
  abundant way.   I’m tired of being sick.  BECOMES  I allow my body toreturn to its 
   Natural, vibrant health. \n\n
 I’m too fat  BECOMES  I honor my body and take good care of it.\n \n
 Nobody loves me.  BECOMES  I radiate love, and love fills my life. \n\n
 I’m not creative.  BECOMES  I am discovering talents I did not 
   know I had. \n\n
 I’m stuck in a lousy job.  BECOMES  Wonderful new doors are opening 
   for me all the time. \n\n
 I’m not good enough.  BECOMES  I amin the process of positive change, 
   and I deserve the best. \n\n
\tThis doesn’t mean that you haveto be worried about every thought you think. When you 
first begin to make the changeoverand really pay attention to your thoughts, you’ll be horrified to 
realize how negative much of your thinking has been. So when you catch a negative thought, just 
think to yourself, That is an old thought; I no longer choose to think that way. Then find a 
positive thought to replace it as quickly as you can. Remember, you want to feel good as much as 
possible. Thoughts of bitterness,resentment, blame, and guilt make you feel miserable. And 
that’s a habit you really want to release. \n\n
\tAnother barrier to allowing positive affirmations to work is feeling “not good enough” – 
that is, you feel that you don’t deserve to have good in your life. If that’s your issue then you 
could begin with Chapter 8 (Self-Esteem). You could see how many of the self-esteem 
affirmations you can memorize, and then repeat them often. Doing so will help change that 
“worthless” feeling you might be carrying around, to one of self-worth. Then watch your positive 
affirmations materialize. \n\n

\tAffirmations are solutions that will replace whatever problem you might have. Whenever 
you have a problem, repeat over and over: 
“All is well. Everything is working out for my highest good. Out of this situation only good will 
come. I am safe”. \n\n
\tThis simple affirmation will work miracles in your life. \n
I would also suggest that you avoid sharing your affirmations with other who may pooh-pooh 
these ideas. When you’re just getting started, it’s best to keepyour thinking to yourself until 
you’ve achieved your desired results. Then your friends will say, “Your life is changing so much. 
You’re so different. Whathave you been doing?”\n\n
Go over this Introduction several times until you really understand the principles and can 
live them. Also, zero in onthe chapter that have the most meaning to you, and practice those 
particular affirmations. And remember tomake up affirmations of your own. 
Some affirmations you can use right now are: \n
“I can fell good about myself!” \n\n
“I can make positive change in my life!” \n\n
“I can do it!”\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n</item>
        <!-- ======================het chuong 1 ============================== -->


        <!-- chuong 2 -->
        <item>
            \n\t\tHealth
\n\n\tIf you want to create better health in your body,there are definitely some things you must 
not do: You must not get angry at your body for any reason. Anger is another affirmation, and it’s 
telling your body that you hate it, or parts of it. Your cells are very aware of every thought you 
have. Think of your body as a servant that’s working as hard asit can to keep you in perfect 
health no matter how you treat it. 
\n\n\t Your body knows how to heal itself. If you feed it health foods and beverages, give it 
exercise and sufficient sleep, and think happy thoughts, then itswork is easy. The cells are 
working in a happy, healthy atmosphere. However, if you’re a couch potato who feeds your body 
junk food and lots of diet soda, and you skimp onsleep and are grouchy and irritable all the time, 
then the cells in your body are working at a disadvantage – they’re in a disagreeable atmosphere. 
If this is the case, it’s no wonder that your body isn’t as healthy as you’d like it to be. 
\n\n\t You’ll never create good heath by talking or thinking aboutyour illness. Good heath 
comes from love and appreciation. You want to put as much love into your body as you possibly 
can. Talk to it and stroke it in loving ways. If there’s a part of your body that’s ailing or dis-eased, 
then you want to treat it as you would a sick littlechild. Tell it how much you love it, and that 
you’re doing everything you can to help it get well quickly. 
\n\n\t If you’re sick, then you want to do more than just go to the doctor and have him or her 
give you a chemical to take care of the symptom. Your body is telling you that something you’re 
doing isn’t good for your body. You need to learn more about health – the more you learn, the 
easier it is to take care of your body. You don’t want to choose to fell like a victim.\nIf you do, 
you’ll just be giving your power away. You could go to a health-food store and pick up one of the 
many good books that teach you how to keep yourself healthy, or you could see a nutritionist and 
have a healthy diet created just for you, but whatever you do,create a healthy, happy mental 
atmosphere. Be a willing participant in your own health plan. 
\n\n\tI believe that we create every so-called illness in our body. The body, like everything else 
in life, is a mirror of our inner thoughts and beliefs. Our body is always talking to us; we just need 
to take the time to listen. Every cell within our body responds to every single thought we think 
and every word we speak. 
 \n\n\tContinuous modes of thinking and speakingproduce body behaviors and postures and 
“eases”, or diseases. The person who has a permanently scowling face didn’t produce that by 
having joyous, loving thoughts. Older people’s faces and bodies so clearly show a lifetime of 
thinking patterns. How will you look when you’re elderly? 
\n\n\t Learn to accept that your life is not a series of random events, but a pathway of awakening. 
If you live every day in this way,you’ll never grow old. You’ll just keep growing. Imagine the 
day you turn 49 as the infancy of another life.A woman who reaches age 50 today and remains 
free of cancer and heart disease can expect to see her 92ndbirthday. You and only you have the 
ability to customize your own life cycle. So change your thinking now and get going! You’re here 
for a very important reason, and everything you need is available to you. 
 \n\n\tYou can choose to think thoughts that create a mental atmosphere that contributes to 
illness, or you can choose to think thoughts that create a healthy atmosphereboth within you and 
around you. 

 \n\n\tPositive Affirmations for Health

\n\n\t-I ENJOY THE FOODS 
THAT ARE BEST FOR MY 
BODY. I LOVE EBERY CELL 
OF MY BODY.
\n\n\t-HEALING HAPPENS! I 
GET MY MIND OUT OF 
THE WAY AND ALLOW THE 
INTELLIGENCE OF MY 
BODY TO DO ITS HEALING 
WORK NATURALLY.

\n\n\t-I LOOK FORWARD TO A 
HEALTHY OLD AGE 
BECAUSE I TAKE LOVING 
CARE FO MY BODY NOW.
\n\n\t-I BALANCE MY LIFE 
BETWEEN WORK, REST, 
AND PLAY. THEY ALL GET 
EQUAL TIME.

\n\n\t-I AM CONTANTLY 
DISCOVERING NEW WAYS 
TO IMPROVE MY HEALTH.
\n\n\t-I AM GRATEFUL TO BE 
ALIVE TODAY. IT IS MY 
JOY AND PLEASURE TO 
LIVE ANOTHER 
WONDERFUL DAY.

\n\n\t-I RETURN MY BODY TO 
OPTIMAL HEALTH BY 
GIVING IT WHAT IT NEEDS 
ON EVERY LEVEL
\n\n\t-I AM WILLING TO ASK 
FOR HELP WHEN I NEED 
IT. I ALWAYS CHOOSE 
THE HEALTH 
PROFESSIONAL WHO IS 
JUST RIGHT FOR MY 
NEEDS.

\n\n\t-I LOVINGLY DO 
EVERYTHING I CAN TO 
ASSIST MY BODY IN 
MAINTAINING PERFECT 
HEALTH.
\n\n\t-I AM THE ONLY PERSON 
WHO HAS CONTROL OVER 
MY EATING HABITS. I CAN 
ALWAYS RESIST 
SOMETHING, IF I CHOOSE 
TO.

\n\n\t-I MAKE HEALTHY 
CHOICES, I HAVE 
RESPECT FOR 
MYSELF.
\n\n\t-I HAVE A SPECIAL 
GUARDIAN ANGEL. I AM 
DIVINELY GUIDED AND 
PROTECTED AT ALL TIMES.
\n\n\t-WATER IS MY FAVORITE 
BEVERAGE. I DRINK LOTS 
OF WATER TO CLEANSE 
MY BODY AND MIND.

\n\n\t-PERFECT HEALTH IS MY 
DIVINE RIGHT, AND I 
CLAIM IT NOW
\n\n\t-FILLING MY MIND WITH 
PLEASANT THOUGHTS IS 
THE QUICKEST ROAD TO 
HEALTH

\n\n\t-I DEVOTE A PORTION OF 
MY TIME TO HELPING 
OTHERS. IT IS GOOD FOR 
MY OWN HEALTH.
\n\n\t-MY HAPPY THOUGHTS 
HELP CREATE MY HEALTH 
BODY.

\n\n\t-I AM GRATEFUL FOR MY 
HEALTHY BODY. I LOVE 
LIFE.
\n\n\t-I BREATHE DEEPLY AND 
FULLY. I TAKE IN THE 
BREATH OF LIFE, AND I 
AN NOURISHED. \n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 3 -->
        <item>
\t\tForgiveness
\n\n\tYou  can  never  be  free  of  bitterness  as 
long  as  you  continue  to  think  unforgiving 
thoughts.  How  can  you  be  happy  in  this 
moment  if  you  continue  to  choose  to  be  angry 
and  resentful?  Thoughts  of  bitterness  can’t 
create joy. No matter how justified you feel you 
are,  no  matter  what  “they”  did,  if  you  insist  on 
holding  on  to  the  past,  then  you  will  never  be 
free.  Forgiving  yourself  and  others  will  release 
you from the prison of the past.
\n\n\tWhen  you  feel  that  you’re  stuck  in  some 
situation,  or  when  you  affirmations  aren’ t 
working,  it  usually  means  that  there’s  more 
forgiveness  work  to  be  done.  When  you  don’t 
flow  freely  with  life  in  the  present  moment,  it 
usually  means  that  you’re  holding  on  to  a  past 
moment.  It  can  be  regret  sadness,  hurt  fear, 
guilt,  blame,  anger,  resentment,  or  sometimes 
even  a  desire  for  revenge.  Each  one  of  these 
states  comes  from  a  space  of  unforgiveness,  a 
refusal  to  let  go  and  come  in  to  the  present 
moment.  Only  in  the  present  moment  can  you 
create your future.
\n\n\tIf you’re holding on  to the past, you  can’t 
be  in  the  present.  It’s  only  in  this  “now” 
moment  that  your  thoughts  and  words  are 
powerful.  So  you  really  don’t  want  to  waste 
your  current  thoughts  by  continuing  to  create 
your future from the garbage of the past.
\n\n\tWhen  you  blame  another,  you  give  your 
own  power  away  because  you’re  placing  the 
responsibility for your feelings on someone else. 
People  in  your  life  may  behave  in  ways  that 
trigger  uncomfortable  responses  in  you. 
However,  they  didn’t  get  into  your  mind  and 
create  the  buttons  that  have  bee n  pushed. 
Taking  responsibility  for  your  own  feelings  and
reactions is mastering your “ability to respond”. 
In other words, you learn to consciously choose 
rather than simply react.
\n\n\tForgiveness  is  tricky  and  confusing 
concept for many people, but know  that  there’s 
a  difference  between  forgiveness  and 
acceptance.  Forgiving  someone  doesn’t  mean 
that  you  condone  their  behavior!  The  act  of 
forgiveness  takes  place  in  your  own  mind.  It 
really  has  nothing  to  do  with  the  other  person. 
The  reality  of  true  forgiveness  lies  in  setting 
yourself free from the pain. It’s simply an act of 
releasing yourself from the negative energy that 
you’ve chosen to hold on to.
\n\n\tAlso,  forgiveness  doesn’t  mean  allowing 
the  painful  behaviours  or  actions  of  another  to 
continue  in  your  life.  Sometimes  forgiveness 
means  letting  go:  You  forgive  that  person  and 
then  you  release  them.  Taking  a  stand  and 
setting  healthy  boundaries  is  often  the  most 
loving  thing  you  can  do  –  not  only  for  yourself, 
but for the other person as well.
\n\n\tNo  matter  what  your  reasons  are  for 
having  bitter,  unforgiving  feelings,  you  can  go 
beyond  them.  You  have  a  choice.  You  can 
choose  to  stay  stuck  and  resentful,  or  you  can 
do  yourself  a  favor  by  willingly  forgiving  that 
happened  in  the  past;  letting  it  go;  and  then 
moving on to create a joyous, fulfilling life. You 
have  the  freedom  to  make  your  life  anything 
you want it  to be because you have freedom of 
choice.
\n\n\tPositive 
Affirmations for Forgiveness

\n\n\t-THE DOOR TO MY HEART OPENS INWARD. I MOVE THROUGH FORGIVENESS TO LOVE.
\n\n\t-THERE IS NO PROBLEM SO BIG OR SO SMALL THAT IT CANNOT BE SOLVED WITH LOVE.

\n\n\t-TODAY I LISTEN TO MY FEELING, AND I AM GENTLE WITH MYSELF, I KNOW THAT ALL OF MY FEELINGS ARE MY FRIENDS
\n\n\t-I AM READY TO BE HEALED. I AM WILLING TO FORGIVE ALL IS WELL

\n\n\t-THE PAST IS OVER, SO 
IT HAS NO POWER NOW. 
THE THOUGHTS OF THIS 
MOMENT CREATE MY 
FUTURE.
\n\n\t-WHEN I MAKE A MISTAKE, I REALZE THAT IT IS ONLY PART OF THE LEARNING PROCESS.

\n\n\t-I GIVE MYSELF THE GIFT OF FREEDOM FROM THE PAST, AND MOVE WITH JOY INTO THE NOW
\n\n\t-I MOVE BEYOND FORGIVENESS TO UNDERSTANDING, AND I HAVE COMPASSION FOR ALL.

\n\n\t-AS I FORGIVE MYSELF, 
IT BECOMES EASIER TO 
FORGIVE OTHERS.

\n\n\t-I KNOW THAT OLD, 
NEGATIVE PATTERNS NO 
LONGER LIMIT ME. I LET 
THEM GO WITH EASE.

\n\n\t-I LOVE AND ACCEPT MY 
FAMILY MEMBERS 
EXACTLY AS THEY ARE 
RIGHT NOW.
\n\n\t-I KNOW THAT I CANNOT 
TAKE PERSONSIBILITY FOR 
OTHER PEOPLE. WE ARE ALL 
UNDER THE LAW OF OUR 
OWN CONSIOUSNESS

\n\n\t-I FOGIVE MYSELF FOR 
NOT BEING PERFECT. I 
AM LIVING THE VERY 
BEST WAY I KNOW HOW.
\n\n\t-EVERYONE IN MY LIFE 
HAS SOMETHING TO TEACH 
ME, WE HAVE A PURPOSE IN 
BEING TOGETHER.

\n\n\t-AS I CHANGE MY 
THOUGHTS, THE 
WORLD AROUND ME 
CHANGES.
\n\n\t-I CANNOT CHANGE 
ANOTHER PERSON. I LET 
OTHERS BE WHO THEY 
ARE, AND I SIMLY LOVE 
WHO I AM
\n\n\t- I FORGIVE EVERYONE IN 
MY PAST FOR ALL 
PERCEIVED WRONGS. I 
RELEASE THEM WITH LOVE.

\n\n\t-IT IS NOW SAFE FOR 
ME TO RELEASE ALL OF 
MY CHILDHOOD TRAUMAS 
AND MOVE INTO LOVE
\n\n\t-ALL OF THE CHANGES IN 
LIFE THAT LIE BEFORE ME 
ARE POSITIVE ONES. I AM 
SAFE.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
            
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 4 -->
        <item>
            
 \n\t\tProsperity
\n\n\tYou can never create prosperity by talking 
or  thinking  about  your  lack  of  money.  This  is 
wasted  thinking  and  cannot  bring  you 
abundance.  Dwelling  on  lack  only  creates  more 
lack.  Poverty  thinking  brings  more  poverty. 
Gratitude thinking brings abundance.
\n\n\tThere are a few negative affirmations and 
attitudes that are guaranteed to keep prosperity 
beyond your reach – for example: “I never have 
enough  money!” That’s  a  terrible  affirmation  to 
use. Another  unproductive  one  is: “Money  goes 
out  faster  than  it  comes  in”. This  is  poverty 
thinking  of  the  worst  kind.  The  Universe  can 
only respond to what you believe about yourself 
and  your  life.Examine  whatever about  yourself 
and  your  life.Example  whatever  negative 
thoughts  you  have  about  money,  and  then 
decide  to  release  them  and  let  them  go.  They 
haven’t served you well in the past and will not 
serve you well in the future.
\n\n\tSometimes  people  think  that  their 
financial  problems  will  be  solved  by  inheriting 
money  from  a  long-lost  relative  or  winning  the 
lottery.  Sure,  you  can  fantasize  about  such 
things,  or  even  buy  an  occasional  lottery  ticket 
for  fun,  but  please  don’t  put  a  lot  of  attention 
on  acquiring  money  in  this  way.  This  is  scarcity 
thinking,  or  poverty  thinking,  and  it  won’t  bring 
lasting  good  into  your  life.  In  fact,  within  two 
years,  most  lottery  winners  have  lost almost  all 
of  their  money,  have  nothing  to  show  for  it, 
and  are  often  worse  off  financially  than  before. 
The problem with money acquired in this way is 
that  is  rarely  solves  a ny  problems.  Why?
Because  it  doesn’t  involve  changing  your 
consciousness.  In  effect,  you’re  saying  to  the 
Universe:  “I  don’t  deserve  to  have  good  in  my
life expect by a fluke chance.”
\n\n\tIf  you  would  only  change  your 
consciousness,  your  thinking,  to  allow  the
abundance of the Universe to flow through your 
experience,  you  could  have  all  the  things  you 
think  the  lottery  could  bring  you.  And  you’d  be 
able  to  keep  them,  for  they  would  be  yours  by 
right  of  consciousness.  Affirming,  declaring, 
deserving,  and  allowing  are  the  steps  to 
demonstrating  riches  far  greater  that  you  could 
ever win in a lottery.
\n\n\tAnother  thing  that  can  keep  you  from 
prospering  is  being  dis-honest.  Whatever  you 
give out comes back to you. Always. If you take 
form Life, then Life will take from  you. You may 
feel  that  you  don’t  steal,  but  are  you  counting 
the  paper  clips  and  stamps  you’re  taking  home 
from the office? Or are you a person who steals 
time  or  robs  others  of  respect  –  or  perhaps 
steals  relationships?  All  these  things  count  and 
are  a  way  of  saying  to  the  Universe:  “I  don’t 
really diverse the good in life. I have to sneak it 
and take it”
\n\n\tBecome  aware  of  the  beliefs  that  may  be 
blocking  the  flow  of  money  in  your  life.  Then 
change  those  beliefs  and  begin  to  create  new, 
abundant  thinking.  Event  if  no  one  else  in  your 
family has done this, you can open your mind to 
the concept of money flowing into your life.
\n\n\tIf you want to prosper, then you must use 
prosperity  thinking.  There  are  two  prosperity
affirmations  that  I’ve  used  for  many  years,  and 
they work well for me. They’ll also work for you. 
\n\n\tThey are:
“My incomes is constantly increasing,”\n
and\n
“I prosper wherever I turn”
\n\n\tI  had  very  little  money  when  I  started 
using these affirmations, but consistent practice 
has made them come true for me

\n\n\tFor  a  long  time,  I’ve  believed  that 
business is a place where we bless and prosper 
each  other.  I’ve  never  understood  the  concept 
of  cutthroat  business,  where  you  try  to  cheat 
and  put  one  over  on  the  other  person.  That 
doesn’t sound like a joyous way to live. There’s 
so much abundance in this world  –  all  we need 
to  do  is  recognize  that  fact  and  share  the 
wealth.
\n\n\tAt  Hay  House,  my  publishing  company, 
we’ve  always  been  honest  and  honorable.  We 
live up to our word, do our work well, and treat 
others  with  respect  and  generosity.  When  you 
live that way, it’s impossible to keep the money 
away;  the  Universe  rewards  you  at  every 
possible  turn.  Today  we  have  a  fabulous 
reputation in the publishing world, and so much 
business  that  we’re  turning  it  away.  We  don’t 
want  to  grow  so  big  that  we  lose  the  personal 
touch.
\n\n\tIf I, an abused child who didn’t finish high 
school,  can  do  it,  you  can,  too.  So  once  a  day, 
stand  with  your  arms  open  wide  and  say  with 
joy:
\n\n\t“I  am  open  and  receptive  to  all  the  good 
and  abundance  in  the  Universe.  Thank  you, 
Life”
\nLife will hear you and respond.
Positive 
\n\n\tAffirmations for Prosperity

\n\n\t-I AM A MAGNET FOR 
MONEY. PROSPERITY OF 
EVERY KIND IS DRAWN TO 
ME.
\n\n\t-I TRULY BELIVE THAT 
WE ARE HERE TO BLESS 
AND PROSPER EACH 
OTHER. I REFLECT THIS 
BELIEF IN MY DAILY 
INTERACTIONS.

\n\n\t-I THINK BIG, AND THEN I 
ALLOW MYSELF TO ACCEPT 
EVEN MORE GOOD FROM 
LIFE
\n\n\t-THE MONEY THAT 
COMES TO ME TODAY I A 
PLEASURE TO HANDLE. I 
SAVE SOME AND SPEND 
SOME.

\n\n\t-WHEREVER IT IS THAT I 
WORK, I AM DEEPLY 
APPRECIATED AND WELL 
COMPENSATED.
\n\n\t-I LIVE IN A LOVING, 
ABUNDANT, HARMONIOUS 
UNIVERSE, AND I AM 
GRATEFUL.

\n\n\t-TODAY IS A DELIGHTFUL 
DAY. MONEY COMES TO 
ME IN EXPECTED AND 
UNEXPECTED WAYS.
\n\n\t-I AM NOW WILLING TO 
BE OPEN TO THE 
UNLIMITED PROSPERITY 
THAT EXISTS 
EVERYWHERE.

\n\n\t-I NOW DO WORK I LOVE, 
AND I AM WELL PAID FOR 
IT.
\n\n\t-I PAY MY BILLS WITH 
LOVE, AND I REJOICE AS I 
WRITE OUT EACH CHECK. 
ABUNDANCE FLOWS 
FREELY THROUGH ME.

\n\n\t-LIFE SUPPLIES ALL MY 
NEEDS IN GREAT 
ABUNDANCE. I TRUST 
LIFE.
\n\n\t-AT THIS VERY MOMENT, 
ENORMOUS WEALTH AND 
POWER ARE AVAILABLE TO 
ME. I CHOOSE TO FEEL 
WORTHY AND DESERVING.

\n\n\t-THE LAW OF 
ATTRACTION BRINGS ONLY 
GOOD INTO MY LIFE.
\n\n\t-I DESERVE THE BEST, 
AND I ACCEPT THE BEST 
NOW

I MAKE HEATHY 
CHOICES, I HAVE 
RESPECT FOR MYSELF
\n\n\t-I MOVE FORM POVERTY 
THINKING TO PROSPERITY 
THINKING TO PROSPERITY 
THINKING, AND MY 
FINANCES REFLECT THIS 
CHANGE.
\n\n\t-I RELEASE ALL 
RESISTANCE TO MONEY, 
AND I NOW ALLOW IT TO 
FLOW JOYOUSLY INTO MY 
LIFE.

\n\n\t-THE MORE GRATEFUL. I 
AM FOR THE WEALTH AND 
ABUNDANCE IN MY LIFE, 
THE MORE REASONS I 
FIND TO BE GRATEFUL.
\n\n\t-MY GOOD COMES FROM 
EVERYWHERE AND 
EVERYONE.

\n\n\t-I EXPRESS GRATITUDE 
FOR ALL THE GOOD IN MY 
LIFE. EACH DAY BRINGS 
WONDERFUL, NEW 
SURPRIES.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 5 -->
        <item>
\n\t\tCreativity
\n\n\tYou  can  never  express  yourself  creatively 
by  talking  or  thinking  about  what  a  klutz  you 
are.  If  you  say,  “I  am  not  creative”  then  that’s 
an  affirmation  that  will  be  true  for  you  for  as 
long as you continue to use it. There’s an i nnate 
creativity  flowing  through  you,  and  if  you  let  it 
out,  it  will  surprise  and  delight  you.  You’re 
tapped  in  to  the  creative  flow  of  energy  in  the 
Universe.  Some  of  you  may  express  yourself 
more  creatively  than  others,  but  everyone  can 
do it.
\n\n\tWe create our lives every day. Each of us 
has  unique  talents  and  abilities.  Unfortunately, 
too  many  of  us  had  well-meaning  adults  stifle 
that  creatively  when  we  were  children.  I  had  a 
teacher  who  once  told  me  I  couldn’t  dance 
because  I  was  too  tall.  A  friend  was  told  he 
couldn’t  draw  because  he  drew  the  wrong  tree. 
It’s  all  so  silly.  But  we  were  obedient  children 
and  believed  the  messages.  Now  we  can  go 
beyond them.
\n\n\tAnother false assumption is that you must 
be an artist to be creative. That’s just one form 
of  creativity,  and  there  are  so  many  more.
You’re  creating  every  moment  of  your  life  –
from  the  most  common,  ordinary  creation  of 
new  cells  in  your  body,  to  your  emotional 
responses,  to  your  present  job,  to  your  bank 
account,  to  your  relationships  with  friends,  and 
to  your  very  attitudes  about  yourself.  It’s  all 
creativity.
\n\n\tAlso,  you  could  be  a  really  good  bed 
maker, you could cook delicious food, you could 
do your job creatively, you could be an artist in 
the  garden,  or  you  could  be  inventive  in  the 
ways in which you’re kind to others. These are a 
few  of  the  millions  of  ways  of  expressing
oneself  creatively.  No  matter  which  way  you 
choose,  you’ll  want  to  feel  satisfaction  and  be 
deeply fulfilled by all that you do.
\nYou’re  divinely  guided  by  Spirit  at  all 
times.  Know  that  Spirit  makes  no  mistakes. 
When  there’s  a  strong  desire  within  you  to
express  or  create  something,  know  that  this 
feeling is Divine discontent. Your longing is your 
calling – and no matter what it is, if you go with 
it,  you’ll  be  guided,  guarded,  and  a ssured  of 
success.  When  a  purpose  or  path  is  laid  before 
you, you have the choice to just trust and  let it 
flow,  or  remain  stuck  in  fear.  Trusting  the 
perfection  that  resides  within  you  is  the  key.  I 
know  that  it  can  be  frightening!  Everybody  is 
afraid  of  something,  but  you  can  do  it  anyway. 
Remember,  the  Universe  loves  you  and  wants 
\nyou to succeed at everything you do.
\nYou’re expressing yourself creatively every 
moment  of  everyday.  You’re  being  you  in  your 
own  unique  way.  Knowing  that,  you  can  now 
release  any  false  mental  beliefs  that  you’re  not 
creative,  and  go  forward  with  each  every 
project that comes to mind.
\n\n\tNever  make  the  mistake  of  thinking  that 
you’re  too  old  for  anything.  My  own  life  didn’t 
begin  to  have  meaning  until  I  was  in  my  mid-40s,  when  I  started  teaching.  At  age  50,  I 
started  my  publishing  company  on  a  very  small 
scale.  At  55,  I  ventured  my  first  garden  and 
have  become  an  avid  organic  gardener  who 
grows  her  own  food.  At  70,  I  enrolled  in  a 
children’s  art  class.  A  few  years  later,  I  totally 
changed my handwriting – I became inspired by 
author  Vimala  Rodgers,  who  wrote  “Your 
handwriting  can  change  your  life”.  At  75,  I 
graduated to an adult art class and have started 
to  sell  my  paintings.  My  current  art  teacher
wants  me  to  get  involved  with  sculpture  next. 
And  recently,  I  took  up  yoga,  and  my  body  in 
making positive changes.
\n\n\tA  few  months  ago,  I  decided  to  stretch 
myself  in  areas  that  scared  me,  and  I  took  up 
ballroom  dancing.  Now  I’m  taking  several 
classes  a  week,  and  I’m  fulfilling  my  childhood 
dream of learning to dance.
\n\n\tI love  to  learn  things  I  haven’t 
experienced.  Who  knows  what  I’ll  do  in  the 
future? What I  do know is  that I’ll be doing my 
affirmations  and  expressing  new  creativity  until 
the day I leave this planet.
\n\n\tIf  there’s  a  particular  project  you  want  to 
work on, or if you just want to be more creative 
in  general,  then  you  can  use  some  of  the 
following affirmations. Use them joyously as you 
release  your  creativity  in  a  million  and  one 
different projects.

\n\n\t
Positive Affirmations for Creativity

\n\n\t-I RELEASE ALL 
RESISTANCE TO 
EXPRESSING MY 
CREATIVITY FULLY.
\n\n\t-I AM SAFE, AND I AM 
FULFILLED IN ALL, THAT I 
DO.

\n\n\t-I AM ALWAYS IN TOUCH 
WITH MY CREATIVE 
SOURCE.
\n\n\t-ALL OF MY CREATVIE 
PROJECT BRING ME GREAT 
SATISFACITON.

\n\n\t-I CREATE EASILY AND 
EFFORTLESSLY WHEN I 
LET MY THOUGHTS COME 
FROM THE LOVING SPACE 
\n\n\t-I KNOW THAT I CAN 
CREATE MIRACLES IN MY 
LIFE.

I AM DISCOVERING
TALENTS I DID NOT 
KNOW I HAD.
OF MY OWN HEART.  XUẤT PHÁT TỪ TRÁI TIM.
\n\n\t-THERE IS AMPLE TIME 
AND OPPORTUNITY FOR 
CREATIVE EXPRESSION IN 
WHATEVER AREA I 
CHOOSE.
\n\n\t-I FEEL GOOD EXPRESSING 
MYSELF IN ALL SORTS OF 
CREATIVE WAYS.

\n\n\t-MY FAMILY TOTALLY 
SUPPORT ME IN 
FULFILLING MY DREAMS.
\n\n\t-I DIRECT MY CREATIVE 
TALENTS TOWARD MUSIC 
ART, DANCE, WRITING –
ANYTHING THAT GIVES ME 
PLEASURE.

\n\n\t-THE KEY TO 
CREATIVITY IS KNOWING 
THAT MY THINKING 
CREATES MY EXPERIENCE. 
I USE THIS KEY IN EVERY 
AREA OF MY LIFE.
\n\n\t-MY TALENTS ARE IN 
DEMAND, AND MY UNIQUE 
GIFTS ARE APPRECIATED BY 
THOSE AROUND ME.

\n\n\t-I AM A CLEAR THINKER, 
AND I EXPRESS MYSELF 
WITH EASE.
\n\n\t-LIFE IS NEVER STUCK, 
STAGNANT, OR STALE, FOR 
EACH MOMENT IS EVERNEW AND FRESH.

\n\n\t-I AM LEARNING TO BE 
MORE CREATIVE EVERY 
DAY.
\n\n\t-MY HEART IS THE CENTER 
OF MY POWER. I FOLLOW 
MY HEART.

\n\n\t-MY JOB ALLOWS ME TO 
EXPRESS MY TALENTS 
AND ABILITIES, AND I 
REJOICE IN THIS 
EMPLOYMENT.
\n\n\t-I AM A JOYOUS, CREATIVE 
EXPRESSION OF LIFE.

\n\n\t-MY POTENTIAL IS 
UNLIMITED.
\n\n\t-IDEAS COME TO ME 
EASILY AND EFFORTLESSLY

\n\n\t-MY INNATE CREATIVITY 
SUPRISES AND DELIGHTS 
ME.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 6 -->
        <item>
 \n\t\tLove and Romance
\n\n\tPersonal relationships always seem to be 
the  first  priority  for  so  many  of  us. 
Unfortunately,  hunting  for  love  doesn’t  always 
attract the right partner because our reasons for 
wanting love may be unclear. We think, Oh, if I 
only had someone who loved me, my life would 
be so much better. That’s not the way it works.
\n\n\tThere’s  a  big  difference  between  the 
need  for  love,  and  being  needy  for  love.  When 
you’re  needy  for  love,  it  means  that  you’re 
missing  love  and  approval  from  the  most 
important  person  you  know-yourself.  You  may 
become  involved  in  relationships  that  are 
codependent and ineffectual for both partners.
You can never create love in your life by 
talking  or  thinking  about  being  lonely.  Feeling 
lonely  and  needy  just  pushes  people  away. Nor 
can  you  heal  a  relationship  in  your  life  by 
talking  or  thinking  about  how  awful  it  is.  This 
only  places  attentions  on  what’s  wrong.  You 
want  to  turn  your  thoughts  that  will  produce  a 
solution.  Arguing  for  your  limitations  is  just 
resistance,  and  resistance  is  simply  a  delay 
tactic. It’s another way of saying. \n“I’m not good 
enough to have what I’m asking for.”
\n\n\tThe  first  relationship  to  improve  is  the 
one you have with yourself. When you’re happy 
with  yourself,  then  all  of  your  other 
relationships  improve,  too.  A  happy  person  is 
very  attractive  to  others.  If  you’re  looking  for 
more love, then you need to love yourself more. 
This  means  no  criticism,  no  complaining,  no 
blaming,  no  whining,  and  no  choosing  to  feel 
lonely.  It  means  being  very  content  with 
yourself in the present moment and choosing to 
think thoughts that make you feel good now.
\n\n\tThere’s  no  one  way  to  experience  love,
for we all experience love in different ways. For 
some  of  us  to  really  experience  love,  we  need 
to feel love, through being hugged and touched. 
Some  of  us  ,  however,  need  to  hear  the  words 
“I  love  you”.  Others  need  to  see  a 
demonstration of love, like a gift of flowers. Our 
preferred way of experiencing love is  often then 
way  we  feel  most  comfortable  demonstrating  it 
back.
\n\n\tI  suggest  that  you  work  on  loving 
yourself nonstop. Demonstrate the growing love 
you have for yourself. Treat yourself to romance 
and  love.  Show  yourself  how  special  you  are. 
Pamper  yourself.  Buy  yourself  flowers  for  your 
home;  and  surround  yourself  with  colors, 
textures,  and  scents  that  please  you.  Life 
always  mirrors  back  to  us  the  feelings  we  have 
inside.  As  you  develop  your  inner  sense  of  love 
and  romance,  the  right  person  to  share  your 
growing sense of intimacy with  will be attracted 
to you like a magnet.
\n\n\tIf  you  want  to  go  from  loneliness 
thinking to fulfillment thinking, then you need to 
think  in  terms  of  creating  a  loving  mental 
atmosphere  within  you  and  around  you.  Do  let 
all  those  negative  thoughts  about  love  and 
romance  just  fade  away;  and  instead,  think 
about  sharing  love,  approval,  and  acceptance 
with everyone you meet.
\n\n\tWhen  you’re  able  to  contribute  to  the 
fulfillment  of  your  own  needs,  then  you  won’t 
be so needy and codependent. It  has to do with 
how  much  you  love  yourself.  When  you  truly 
love  who  you  are,  you  stay  centered,  calm  and 
secure,  and  your  relationships  at  home  as  well 
as  at  work  are  wonderful.  You’ll  find  yourself 
reacting  to  various  situations  and  people 
differently.  Matters  that  once  may  have  been
desperately  important  won’t  seem  quite  as 
crucial anymore. New people will enter your life, 
and perhaps some old ones will disappear – this 
can be kind of scary at first  –  but it can also be 
wonderful, refreshing and exciting.
\n\n\tOnce  you’re  clear  about  this  issue  in 
your  mind,  and  you  know  what  you  want  in  a 
relationship,  you  must  go  out  and  be  with 
people.  No  one  is  going  to  suddenly  appear  at 
your doorstep. A good way to  meet people is in 
a  support  group  or  night  class.  These  types  of 
get-togethers  enable  you  to  connect  with 
people who are like-minded or who are involved 
in  the  same  pursuits.  It’s  amazing  how  quickly 
you  can  meet  new  friends.  Be  open  and 
receptive, and the Universe will respond to you, 
bringing you your highest good.
\n\n\tRemember,  when  you  think  joyous 
thoughts,  you’ll  be  a  happy  person,  everyone 
will want to be with you, and all of your current 
relationships will improve.

\n\n\tPositive Affirmations for Love and Romance



\n\n\t-FROM TIME TO TIME, I 
ASK THOSE I LOVE, “HOW 
CAN I LOVE YOU MORE?”
\n\n\t-I HAVE COME TO THIS 
PLANET TO LEARN TO 
LOVE MYSELF MORE, AND 
TO SHARE THAT LOVE 
WITH ALL THOSE AROUND 
ME.

\n\n\t-I CHOOSE TO SEE 
CLEARLY WITH EYES OF 
LOVE. I LOVE WHAT I SEE
\n\n\t-LIFE IS VERY SIMPLE. 
WHAT I GIVE OUT COMES 
BACK TO ME. TODAY I 
CHOOSE TO GIVE LOVE.

I DRAW LOVE AND 
ROMANCE INTO MY 
LIFE, AND I ACCEPT 
IT NOW
\n\n\t-LOVE HAPPENS! I 
RELEASE THE DESPERATE 
NEED FOR LOVE, AND 
INSTEAD, ALLOW IT TO 
FIND ME IN THE PERFECT 
TIME-SPACE SEQUENCE.
\n\n\t-I REJOICE IN THE LOVE I 
ENCOUNTER EVERY DAY.

\n\n\t-I NOW DESERVE LOVE, 
ROMANCE, AND JOY – AND 
ALL THE GOOD THAT LIFE 
HAS TO OFFER ME.
\n\n\t-I AM COMFORTABLE 
LOOKING IN THE MIRROR, 
SAYING, “I LOVE YOU, I 
REALLY LOVE YOU”

\n\n\t-LOVE IS ALL THERE IS!  \n\n\t-LOVE IS AROUND EVERY 
CORNER, AND JOY FILLS 
MY ENTIRE WORLD.

\n\n\t-I AM SURROUNDED BY 
LOVE, ALL IS WELL.
\n\n\t-I AM BEAUTIFUL, AND 
EVERYBODY LOVES ME, I 
AM GREETED BY LOVE 
WHEREVER I GO.

\n\n\t-MY HEART IS OPEN. I 
SPEAK WITH LOVING 
WORDS
\n\n\t-I AM SAFE IN ALL MY 
RELATIONSHIPS, AND I 
GIVE AND RECEIVE LOTS 
OF LOVE.

\n\n\t-I HAVE A WONDERFUL 
LOVER, AND WE ARE BOTH 
HAPPY AND AT PEACE
\n\n\t-I ATTRACT ONLY 
HEALTHY RELATIONSHIPS. 
I AM ALWAYS TREATED 
WELL.

\n\n\t-I AM IN A JOYOUS, 
INTIMATE RELATIONSHIP 
WITH A PERSON WHO 
TRULY LOVES ME.
\n\n\t-I AM VERY THANKFUL 
FOR ALL THE LOVE IN MY 
LIFE. I FIND IT 
EVERYWHERE.

\n\n\t-I COME FROM THE 
LOVING SPACE OF MY 
HEART, AND I KNOW THAT 
LOVE OPENS ALL DOORS.
\n\n\t-LONG-LASTING, LOVING 
RELATIONSHIPS BRIGHTEN 
MY LIFE.n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n

            
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 7 -->
        <item>
\n\t\tJob success
\n\n\tFinding  success  in  a  career  is  a  major 
problem  for  many  people.  However,  you  can 
always have a successful job if you simply change 
the  way  you  think  about  work.  You’ll  never  find 
work a pleasure if you hate your job or  you can’t 
stand  your  boss.  What  a  terrible  affirmation  that 
is.  It  will  be  impossible  for  you  to  ever  attract  a 
great  job  with  that  belief  system.  If  you  want  to 
enjoy  your  time  at  work,  then  you  must  change 
your  thinking.  I’m  a  great  believer  in  blessing 
every  person,  place, and  thing  in  the  work-place 
with love. Begin with your current job: Affirm that 
it  is  merely  a  stepping-stone  to  far  greater 
positions.
\n\n\tYou’re in your current job because of things 
you  believed  in  the  past.  You  drew  it  to  you  by 
your  thinking.  (Perhaps  you  learned  you  attitude 
toward work from your parents). No matter  – you 
can change your thinking now. So bless with love 
your  boss,  your  co-workers,  the  location,  the 
building,  the  elevators  or  stairs,  the  offices,  the 
furniture,  and  each  and  every  customer.  This 
creates  a  loving  mental  atmosphere  within  you, 
and the entire environment will respond to it.
\n\n\tI’ve never understood the reasoning behind 
belittling  or  berating  others  at  work.  If  you’re an 
owner, a manager, or a supervisor, how can you 
possibly  expect  to  get  the  best  work  from  others 
if  they’re  frightened  or  resentful?  We  all  want  to 
be  appreciated,  acknowledged,  and  encouraged. 
If  you  support  your  employees  and  give  them 
respect,  then  they’ll  give  you  the  best  work  they 
can.
\n\n\tPlease  don’t  believe  that  it’s  hard  to  get  a 
job.  That  may  be  true  for  many,  but  it  doesn’t 
have  to  be  true  for  you.  You  only  need  one  job, 
and  your  consciousness  will  then  open  the 
pathway  for  you.  Don’t  have  faith  in  fear.  When 
you hear of negative trends in  business or in  the 
economy, immediately  affirm: “It may be true for 
some,  but  it  is  not  true  for  me.  I  always  prosper 
no matter where I am or what is going on.”
\n\n\tPeople  often  ask  me  for  affirmations  to 
make  their  relationships  at  work  smoother.  In 
fact,  for  many  people  this  is  a  really  big  issue  in 
their lives. I’m deeply aware that whatever I give 
out  comes  back  to  me  multiplied.  This  is  true 
everywhere,  including  at  work.  In  the  workplace, 
it’s  important  to  know  that  every  employee  (and 
employer)  has  been  attracted  by  the  action  of 
love,  for  it’s  his  or  her  Divine  right  place  here  at 
this  very  moment.  Divine  harmony  permeates  us 
all, and we can flow together in the workplace in 
a most productive and joyous way.

\n\n\tThere  aren’t  any  problems  that  don’t  have
solutions.  There  aren’t  any  questions  without 
answers.  Choose  to  go  beyond  the  problem  to 
seek  the  Divine  solution  to  any  type  of   discord 
that  seems  to  appear.  Be  willing  to  learn  from 
any  strife  or  confusion  as  it  comes  up.  It’s 
important  to  release  whatever  pattern  may  be  in 
your  consciousness  that  has  contributed  to  the 
situation.
\n\n\tYou  know  that  you’re  successful  in  all  that 
you do. You’re inspired and productive. You serve 
others willingly and gladly. Divine harmony reigns 
supreme  within  and  around  you  and  within  and 
around each and every person in your workplace.
If you like your job but feel that you’re not 
getting  paid  enough,  then  bless  you  current 
salary  with  love.  Expressing  gratitude  for  what 
you have now enables your income to grow. And 
please, absolutely no more complaining about the 
job  or  your  co-workers.  Your  consciousness  put
you  where  you  are  now.  Your  changing 
consciousness  can  lift  to  you  a  better  position. 
\nYou can do it!
\n\n\tDuring  your  workday,  there  a  number  of 
things  you  can  do  to  release  tension.  Here  are a 
few of my suggestions:\n\n
1.Before  you  go  to  work  every  day,  do  this 
simple  exercise:  Just  sit  comfortably  and 
concentrate on your breath. Whenever you notice 
thoughts  coming  in,  gently  bring  you’re 
awareness  back  to  your  breath.  Give  yourself  at 
least  10  or  15  minutes  to  dwell  in  the  silence 
each  day.  There’s  nothing  difficult  or  tricky  to 
this.\n\n
2.Write  or  type  this  affirmation  and  put  it 
where you can see it at work every day:
“My job is a peaceful haven. I bless my job 
with love. I put love in every corner, and my job 
lovingly responds with warmth and comfort. I am 
at peace.”\n
When  you  start  to  think  about  your  boss, 
say this affirmation to yourself:
“I  only  give  out  that  which  I  wish  to 
receive.  My  love  and  acceptance  of  others  is 
mirrored to me in every way.”\n
Refuse to be limited in any  way by humanmind  thinking.  Your  life  can  be  filled  with  love 
and  joy  because  your  work  is  a  Divine  idea. 
Remember  to  say  to  yourself  every  day  before 
going to work:\n\n
“No  matter  where  I  am,  there  is  only 
infinite  good,  infinite  wisdom,  infinite  harmony, 
and infinite love.”

\n\n\tPositive affirmations for Job Success

\n\n\t-THE JOY I FIND IN MY 
CAREER IS REFECTED IN MY 
OVERALL HAPPINESS
\n\n\t-I TRULY BELIEVE THAT 
WE ARE HERE TO BLESS 
AND PROSPER EACH 
OTHER. I REFECT THIS 
BELIEF IN MY DAILY 
INTERACTIONS

\n\n\t-MAKING DECISIONS IS 
EASY FOR ME, I WELLCOME 
NEW IDEAS AND I FOLLOW 
THROUGH WITH WHAT I 
SAY.
\n\n\t-I CHOOSE HEALTHY 
STIMULAION. DURING 
BREAKS AT WORK, I SPEAK 
POSITIVELY WITH OTHERS 
AND LISTEN WITH 
COMPASSION.

\n\n\t-AT MY JOB, MY COWORKERS AND I ENCORAGE 
EACH OTHER’S GROWTH 
AND SUCCESS
\n\n\t-I AM AT EASE SPEAKING 
IN FRONT OF OTHERS. I 
HAVE CONFIDENCE IN 
MYSELF.

\n\n\t-WHEN I WAKE UP IN THE 
MORNING, I PLAN FOR A 
GOOD DAY. MY 
ANTICUPATION ATTRACTS 
POSITIVE EXPERIENCES TO 
ME.
\n\n\t-I CREATE A GOOD 
FEELING AT WORK. I 
REALIZE THAT THERE ARE 
LAWS THAT GOVERN THE 
UNIVERSE, AND I WORK 
WITH THESE LAWS IN 
EVERY AREA OF MY LIFE.

\n\n\t-THE PERFECT JOB IS 
LOOKING FOR ME, AND WE 
ARE BEING BROUGHT 
TOGETHER NOW.
\n\n\t-I DESERVE TO HAVE A 
SUCCESSFUL CAREER, AND 
I ACCEPT IT NOW.

\n\n\t-WHEN I ENCOUNTER 
PROBLEMS ON THE JOB, I 
AM WILLING TO ASK FOR 
HELP.
\n\n\t-EVERYONE I ENCOUNTER 
AT WORK TODAY HAS MY 
BEST INTEREST AT HEART.

\n\n\t-I KNOW THAT WHEN I DO 
MY BEST AT MY JOB, I AM 
REWARDED IN ALL SORTS 
OF WAYS
\n\n\t-MY JOB SUPPORTS THE 
UNFOLDMENT OF MY 
HIGHEST POTENTIAL. I AM 
SUCCESSFUL AT 
EVERYTHING I DO.

\n\n\t-WHEN IT IS TIME FOR A 
NEW JOB, THE PERFECT 
POSITION PRESENT 
ITSELF EASILY
\n\n\t-OPPORTUNITIES ARE 
EVERYWHERE. I HAVE A 
MULTITUDE OF CHOICES
\n\n\t-I AM VERY GOOD AT 
GIVING ENCORAGEMENT 
AND POSITIVE FEEDBACK 
TO OTHERS

\n\n\t-I AM THE STAR IN MY 
OWN MOVIE. I AM ALSO 
THE WRITER AND THE 
DIRECTOR. I CREATE 
WONDERFUL ROLES FOR 
MYSELF IN MY WORK 
ENVIRONMENT.
\n\n\t-I HAVE UNLIMITED 
POTENTIAL. ONLY GOOD 
LIFE BEFORE ME

\n\n\t-WORKING TOGETHER IS 
PART OF THE PURPOSE OF 
LIFE. I LOVE THE PEOPLE I 
WORK WITH.
\n\n\t-MY WORKPLACE IS A 
PLEASURE TO BE IN. THERE 
IS MUTUAL RESPECT 
AMONG MY CO-WORKERS.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 8 -->
        <item>
     \n\t\tStress – Free living
\n\n\tThis  is  the  moment  in  which  you’re either 
enjoying  or  not  enjoying  your  life.  What  you’re 
thinking  is  creating  the  way  you  feel  in  your 
body  right  now,  and  it’s  also  creating  your 
experiences of tomorrow. If you’re stressing out 
over  every  little  thing  and  making  mountains 
out of molehills, you’ll never find inner peace.
\n\n\tWe  talk  a  lot  about  stress  these  days. 
Everyone  seems  to  be  stressed  out  by 
something.  Stress  seem  to  be  a  buzzword,  and 
we  use  it  to  the  point  where  I  think  it’s  a  copout:  “I’m  so  stressed,”  or  “This  is  so  stressful,” 
or “All this stress, stress, stress.”
\n\n\tI think  that stress is an fearful reaction to 
life’s  constant  changes.  It’s  an  excus e  we  often 
use for not taking responsibility for our feelings. 
If  we  can  put  the  blame  out  there  on someone 
or  something,  then  we  can  just  play  the 
innocent  victim.  Being  the  victim  doesn’t  make 
us  feel  good,  and  it  doesn’t  change  the 
situation.
\n\n\tOften  we’re  stressing  ourselves  out 
because  we  have  our  priorities  mixed  up.  So 
many  of  us  feel  that  money  is  the  most 
important  thing  in  our  lives.  This  is  simply  not 
true. There’s something far more important and 
precious to us  –  without which we couldn’t live. 
What is that? It’s our breath.
\n\n\tOur breath is the most precious substance 
in  our  lives,  and  yet  we  totally  take  it  for 
granted  that  when  we  exhale,  our  next  breath 
will  be  there.  If  we  didn’t  take  another  breath, 
we  couldn’t  last  three  minutes.  Now  if  the 
Power  that  created  us  has  given  us  enough 
breath  to  last as  long as  we  shall  live,  can’t  we 
have faith that everything else we need will also 
be supplied?
\n\n\tWhen  we  trust  Life  to  take  care  of  all  our 
little problems, then stress just melts away.
\n\n\tYou don’t have  time to waste on negative 
thinking  or  emotions,  because  that  only  creates 
more of what you say you don’t want.  If you’re 
doing some positive affirmations and you’re not 
getting the results you desire, then check to see 
how  often  during  the  day  you  allow  yourself  to 
feel bad or upset. These emotions are probably 
just  the  thing  that’s  frustrating  you,  delaying 
the  manifestation  of  your  affirmations,  and 
stopping the flow of your good.
\n\n\tThe  next  time  you  realize  how  stressed 
you are, ask yourself what’s scaring you. Stress 
is  just  fear,  it’s  that  simple.  You  don’t  need  to 
be afraid of life or your own emotions. Find out 
what you’re doing to yourself that’s creating this 
fear within you. You inner goal is joy, harmony, 
and  peace.  Harmony  is  being  at  peace  with 
yourself.  It’s  not  possible  to  have  stress  and 
inner  harmony  at  the  same  time.  When  you’re 
at peace, you do one thing at a time. You don’t 
let things get to you.
\n\n\tSo when you feel stressed, do something 
to release the fear: breathe deeply or go for a 
brisk walk. Affirm to yourself:\n
“I am the only power in my world; and I 
create a peaceful, loving, joyful, fulfilling life.”\n
\n\n\tYou wan to move through life feeling safe. 
Don’t give a little world like stress a lot of 
power. Don’t use it as an excuse for creating 
tension in your body. Nothing – no person, 
place or thing – has any power over you. You’re 
the only thinker in your mind, and your 
thoughts are the ones that create your life.
\n\n\tSo train yourself to think thoughts that 
make you feel good. That way you’ll always be 
creating your life out of joy and in joy. Joy
always be creating your life out of joy and in 
joy. Joy always brings more to be joyous about.

\n\n\tPositive Affirmations for Stress-Free Living

\n\n\t-I LET GO OF ALL FEAR 
AND DOUBT, AND LIFE 
BECOMES SIMLE AND 
EASY FOR ME.

\n\n\t-I AM EVEN-TEMPERED 
AND EMOTIONALLY WELLBALLANCED.

\n\n\t-I CREATE A STRESSFREE WORLD FOR 
MYSELF.

\n\n\t-I AM SAFE WHEN I 
EXPRESS MY FEELINGS, I 
CAN BE SERENE IN ANY 
SITUATIONS.

\n\n\t-I RELAX ALL OF MY 
NECK MUSCLES, AND I 
LET GO OF ANY TENSION 
IN MY SHOULDERS.

\n\n\t-I HAVE WONDERFUL 
RELATIONSHIPS WITH MY 
FRIENDS, FAMILY 
MEMBERS, AND COWORKERS, I AM 
APPRECIATED.

\n\n\t-I SLOWLY BREATHE IN 
AND OUT, AND I FIND 
MYSELF RELAXING MORE 
AND MORE WITH EACH 
BREATH.

\n\n\t-I AM COMFORTABLE WITH 
MY FINANCES. I AM ALWAYS 
ABLE TO PAY MY BILLS ON 
TIME.

\n\n\t-I AM CAPABLE PERSON, 
AND I CAN HANDLE 
ANYTHING THAT COMES 
MY WAY.

\n\n\t-FINANIAL SECURITY PUTS 
ME AT EASE AND MAKES ME 
FEEL GOOD ABOUT MY 
FUTURE.

\n\n\t-I AM CENTERED AND 
FOCUSED, I FEEL MORE 
SECURE EACH DAY.

\n\n\t-I AM WILLING TO LEARN. 
THE MORE I LEARN, THE 
MORE I GROW.

\n\n\t-I AM ALWAYS IN A 
LOVING ATMOSPHERE –
BOTH AT HOME AND AT 
WORK.

\n\n\t-NO MATTER HOW OLD I 
AM, I CAN ALWAYS LEARN 
MORE, AND I DO SO WITH 
CONFIDENCE.

\n\n\t-I REALIZE THAT 
STRESS Í ONLY FEAR. 
I NƠ RELEASE ALL 
FEARS.

\n\n\t-I TRUST MYSELF TO 
DEAL WITH ANY 
PROBLEMS THAT ARISE 
DURING THE DAY.

\n\n\t-I MEDITATE ON A 
RECULAR BASIS AND REAP 
BENEFITS FROM THIS 
PRACTICE.

\n\n\t-WHEN I FEEL TENSE, I 
REMEMBER TO RELAX ALL 
OF THE MUSCLES AND 
ORGANS OF MY BODY.

\n\n\t-I CLOSE MY EYES, THINK 
POSITIVE THOUGHTS, AND 
BREATHE GOODNESS IN 
AND OUT.

\n\n\t-I LET GO OF ALL 
NEGATIVITY THAT RESTS 
IN MY BODY AND MIND.

\n\n\t-I AM IN THE PROCESS 
OF MAKING POSITIVE 
CHANGES IN ALL AREAS 
OF MY LIFE.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 9 -->
        <item>
            
            \n\t\tSelf-Esteem
\n\n\tYou’ll never have good self-esteem if you 
have negative thoughts about yourself.
\n\n\tSelf-esteem is merely feeling good about 
yourself, and then you do so, you develop 
confidence. Confidence then builds self-esteem 
each step feeds upon the other. Once you get 
the rhythm going, you can accomplish almost 
anything.
\n\n\tSince self-esteem is what you think about 
yourself, you have the freedom to think 
anything you want. So why would you want to 
belittle yourself?
\n\n\tYou were born extremely confident. You 
came into this world knowing how wonderful 
you are. You were so perfect when you were a 
tiny baby. You didn’t have to do anything  – you 
were already perfect – and you acted as if you 
were aware of that. You knew you were the 
center of the Universe. You weren’t afraid to 
ask for what you wanted. You freely expressed 
your emotions. Your mother knew when you 
were angry; in fact, the entire neighborhood 
knew it. And when you were happy, your smile 
lit up the whole room. You were so full of love 
and confidence.
\n\n\tLittle babies will die if they don’t get love. 
Once we’re older, we learn to live without love, 
but nobody will stand for that. Babies also love 
every inch of their bodies. They have no guilt, 
no shame, no comparisons. They know they’re 
unique and wonderful.
\n\n\tYou were like that. Then somewhere 
during your childhood, your well-meaning 
parents passed on their own insecure feeling 
and taught you feelings of inadequacy and fear. 
At that point, you began to deny your own 
magnificence. These thoughts and feelings were
never true, and they certainly aren’t true now. 
So I want to bring you back to the time when 
you really knew how to love yourself by talking 
about mirror work.
\n\n\tMirror work is simple and very powerful. It 
simply involves looking into a mirror when you 
say your affirmations. Mirrors reflect your true 
feelings back to us. As children, we received 
most of our negative messages from adults, 
many of them looking us straight in the eye and 
perhaps even shaking a finger at us. Today, 
when most of us look into a mirror, we’ll say 
something negative. We either criticize our 
looks, or berate ourselves, for something else.
\n\n\tTo look yourself in the eye and make a
positive declaration is one of the quickest way 
to get positive results with affirmations. I ask 
people to look in their eyes and say something 
positive about themselves every time they pass 
a mirror.
\n\n\tIf something unpleasant happens to you 
during the day, immediately go to the mirror 
and say: “I love you anyway” Events come and 
go, but the love you have for yourself can be 
constant, and it’s the most important quality 
you possess in life. If something wonderful 
happens, go to the mirror and say, “Thank 
you.” Acknowledge yourself for creating this 
wonderful experience.
\n\n\tFist thing in the morning and last thing in 
the evening, I want you to look into your eyes 
and say: “I love you, I really love you. And I 
accept you exactly as you are” It can be tough 
at first, but if you stick with it, in a short time 
this affirmation will be true for you. Won’t that 
be fun!
\n\n\tYou’ll find that as your self-love grows, so 
will your self-respect, and any changes that you
find yourself needing to make will be easier to 
accomplish when you know that they’re the 
right ones for you. Love is never outside 
yourself  - it’s always within you. As you’re more 
loving, you’ll be more lovable.
\n\n\tSo choose new thoughts to think about 
yourself, and choose new words to tell yourself 
how magnificent you are and that you deserve 
all the good that Life has to offer.
\n\n\tPositive Affirmations for Self-esteem

\n\n\t-I AM TOTALLY 
ADEQUATE FOR ALL 
SITUATIONS.
\n\n\t-I AM LOVED AND 
ACCEPTED EXACTLY AS I 
AM, RIGHT HERE AND 
RIGHT NOW.

\n\n\t-I CHOOSE TO FEEL 
GOOD ABOUT MYSELF. I 
AM WORTHY OF MY OWN 
LOVE.
\n\n\t-I SEE THE WORLD 
THROUGH EYES OF LOVE 
AND ACCEPTANCE. ALL IS 
WELL IN MY WORLD.

\n\n\t-I STAND ON MY OWN 
TWO FEET. I ACCEPT AND 
USE MY OWN POWER.
\n\n\t-MY SELF-ESTEEM IS HIGH 
BECAUSE I HONOR WHO I 
AM

\n\n\t-IT IS SAFE FOR ME TO 
SPEAK UP FOR MYSELF.
\n\n\t-MY LIFE GETS MORE 
FABULOUS EVERY DAY. I 
LOOK FORWARD TO WHAT 
EACH NEW HOUR BRINGS.

\n\n\t-IT DOES NOT MATTER 
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE 
SAY OR DO. WHAT 
MATTERS IS HOW I 
CHOOSE TO REACT AND 
WHAT I CHOOSE TO
BELIEVE ABOUT MYSELF.
\n\n\t-I AM NEITHER TOO 
LITTLE NOR TOO MUCH, 
AND I DO NOT HAVE TO 
PROVE MYSELF TO ANYONE.

\n\n\t-I AM RADIANT BEING 
ENJOYING LIFE TO 
THE FULLEST.
\n\n\t-I TAKE A DEEP BREATH 
AND ALLOW MYSELF TO 
RELAX. MY ENTIRE BODY 
CALMS DOWN.
\n\n\t-LIFE SUPPORTS ME IN 
EVERY POSSIBLE WAY.

\n\n\t-TODAY, NOPERSON, 
PLACE, OR THING CAN 
IRRITATE OR ANNOY ME. 
I CHOOSE TO BE AT 
PEACE.
\n\n\t-THIS IS THE ONLY TIME I 
GET TO LIVE TODAY. I 
CHOOSE TO ENJOY IT.

\n\n\t-MY CONSCIOUSNESS IS 
FILLED WITH HEALTHY, 
POSITIVE, LOVING 
THOUGHTS THAT 
REFLECT THEMSELVES IN 
MY EXPERIENCE.
\n\n\t-I HAVE THE SELF-ESTEEM, 
POWER, AND CONFIDENCE 
TO MOVE FORWARD IN LIFE 
WITH EASE.

\n\n\t-I MOVE THROUGH LIFE 
AND KNOW THAT I AM 
SAFE DIVINELY 
PROTECTED AND GUIDED
\n\n\t-THE GREATEST GIFT I 
CAN GIVE MYSELF IS 
UNCONDITIONAL LOVE.

\n\n\t-I ACCEPT OTHERS AS 
THEY ARE; AND THEY, IN 
TURN, ACCEPT ME.
\n\n\t-I LOVE MYSELF EXACTLY 
AS I AM. I NO LONGER 
WAIT TO BE PERFECT IN 
ORDER TO LOVE MYSELF.n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
            
        </item>
        <!-- chuong 10 -->
        <item>
            \n\t\tIn Conclusion
\n\n\tOnce you’ve done your affirmations, then it’s 
time to release them and let them go. You’ve 
decided that you want. You’ve affirmed relea se 
them to the Universe so that the laws of Life can 
bring them to you.
\n\n\tIf you worry and fret about how your 
affirmations will come true, you’re just delaying the 
whole process. It’s not your job to figure out how to 
bring your affirmations to fruition. They way the 
Laws of Affirmation work, you declare that you have
something, and then the Universe brings it to you. 
The Universe is far more clever than you are and 
knows every possible way to make your affirmations 
come true. The only reason for delay and for 
seemingly denying you is that there’s a part of you 
that doesn’t believe that you diverse it. Or perhaps 
your beliefs are so strong that they overpower your 
affirmations.
\n\n\tIf you’re declaring: “My income is increasing” 
and it isn’t, then perhaps you have  old, deep-seated 
beliefs that you don’t deserve to prosper. Or maybe 
your family had strong negative beliefs about 
money, and there’s a part of you that still accepts 
those beliefs.
\n\n\tAs little children, we’re so obedient that we’re 
willing to accept our parents’ beliefs about life and 
continue to operate under them for the rest of our 
lives… until we choose to really look at those beliefs 
and examine them.
\n\n\tYour mother or father may have constantly 
said, “Oh, money is hard to come by.” Now without 
even knowing it, you still have that belief in your 
own consciousness. If you believe that, then the 
Universe can’t bring you more income until you 
release that thought.
\n\n\tI often ask people to look at what their 
family’s beliefs were about various subjects. If 
prosperity is you issue, then take out a large sheet 
of paper and write down all the things your family 
said about money when you were a child. If you 
find any negative statements (remember these were 
all affirmations for your family members), then your 
job is to turn those negative beliefs into positive 
affirmations. Free yourself from the tyranny of your 
parents’ negative affirmations, and you’ll open 
yourself to the abundant flow of good in every area 
of your life.
\n\n\tPlease don’t be discouraged by any setbacks. 
You’re learning a new process. As you become 
proficient at it, your life will become easier and 
easier.
\n\n\tRemember…
\n\n\n\t
No matter how wonderful the present moment 
is, the future can be even more fulfilling and joyous. 
The Universe always waits in smiling repose for us 
to align our thinking with its laws. When we are in 
alignment, everything flows. It is possible. You can 
do it. I can do it. We can do it. Make the effort. You 
will be so pleased. Your whole world will change for 
the better\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>